E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Publication listings
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1937 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1938; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1939; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1940; 3 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1941; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1942 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1943; 4 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1944; 4 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1945; 6 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1929 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Publications, 1930; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - "A List of 1931 Publications and of changes in the Prices of Books Published by E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. Supplementary to Their Catalouge of 1930", 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1933 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1936 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1937 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1938; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1939 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1941; 5 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1942; 5 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1943; 4 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1944; 5 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1945; 4 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1946 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1948 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1950; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1951; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc. 100 YEAR ANNIVERSARY, 1952 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1954; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Publications E.P. Dutton and Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Books of Quality Spring E.P. Duton and Company, 1932 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Books for Presents - The Best Bookstore E.P. Dutton and Company (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Gift Suggestions from E.P. Dutton and Company (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Company's Holiday Books for 1902 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Company's Calendars, Booklets, Toy-books, etc. for the Holiday Season, 1903-04 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Christmas Books Published by E.P. Dutton and Company for the Year of 1906 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Christmas Books, 1907 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - For the Holiday Season Dutton's Christmas Cards, Calendars and Books, 1908-1909 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Christmas Books, 1908 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Catalogue of Christmas Books for 1911 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - New and Illustrated Holiday Books, 1912-1913; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - New and Illustrated Holiday Books, 1913-1914 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - New and Illustrated Holiday Books, 1915-1916 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Books for Christmas ( 1920?) (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - A List of Books Suitable for Holiday Gifts, 1922-23 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Books for Gifts (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Easter Line - Easter Stock, 1908 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Valentines - Stock (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Valentines - Valentine Stock, 1908 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - The Dutton Calendars for 1908 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co.'s List of Calendars, Booklets Color, Toy and Gift Books, etc. Holiday Season, 1900 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co.'s List of Calendars, Booklets, Color, Toy and Gift Books, etc. Holiday Season, 1901 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co.'s List of Calendars, Booklets, Color, Toy and Gift Books, etc. Holiday Season, 1903 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Catalogue of Calendars, 1909-10; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Catalogue of Calendars, 1910-11; 2 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Art Calendars Season, 1912; 3 copies (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Art Calendars Season 1913 (Box 8)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Art Calendars Season 1914 (Box 8)
  - Pamphlet - The Story of "Everyman" by J.M. Dent - "Everyman" pamphlet, No.2, 8 copies (Box 9)
  - Pamphlet - No.6 (E. Pamo) by Ernest Rhys (Box 9)
  - Pamphlet - Books for Young People by Brian Rhys - "Everyman" pamphlet, No.7 (Box 9)
  - Pamphlet - The Great Travelers and Explorers by Brian Rhys - "Everyman" pamphlet, No.8 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Ernest Nister Season Fine Art, Fancy, Block, Pocket, and Purse Calendars (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Ernest Nister's Catalouge, 1905 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books for Boys and Girls, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton's Monthly Bulletin: A Journal of Book Comment, June 1913; 18 copies (Box 9)
  - Book - The Day's Play by A.A. Milne (Box 9)
    See also:
    Milne I through Milne VIII in Publicity files (Box 47),
    Authors: Milne, A. A. (Box 11)
    Childrens' editors files: Mellin - Milne and Milne-Mudro (Box 77)
    Three books in production files: Birthday Party and Other Stories (Box 18), Milne Pop up Book (Box 20), and Peace With Honor (Box 21).
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books for Boys and Girls, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books for Boys and Girls, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books for Boys and Girls, 1936 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Books "To Grow On" (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books for Boys and Girls, 1938 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - A List of Books for Children (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Children's Holiday Books (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Co.'s Calendars, Booklets, Color, Toy and Gift Books for the Holiday Season, 1899 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton and Company's Holiday Books for Young People December, 1901 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - New and Illustrated Holiday Books for Children (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - New and Illustrated Children's Books for the Holiday Season, 1909-1910; 2 copies (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1912; 2 copies (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1913 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1914 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1915; 3 copies (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1923 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1924 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1927 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1928 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1948 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children CELEBRATING 100 YEARS OF PUBLISHING, 1952 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1932 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1939; 2 copies (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1941 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - E.P. Dutton's Books For Children, 1942 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books For Spring, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Catalogue - Dutton Books For Fall, 1957; 3 copies (Box 9)
  - Album, contains various catalogues and clippings (Box 9)
  - Album, contains various catalogues and clippings (Box 9)
- General files
  - Centennial History of E.P. Dutton, Inc., 1952 (Box 9)
  - Agents, 1939-1944 (Box 9)
  - Authors: Photos (Box 9)
  - Authors: Reconstruction (Box 9)
  - Book Prices, 1932-1943 (Box 9)
  - Book Prices, 1944-1946 (Box 9)
  - Church Publishing, Dutton, E.P. (1852-1879) Mr. Dutton's Accounts of First Years (Box 10)
  - Copyright, 1918 (Box 10)
  - Corres. Brooks, Van Wyck, 1919-1945 (Box 10)
    Brooks, Van Wyck Correspondence #1 (1919-1921)
    Brooks, Van Wyck Correspondence #2 (1922-1936)
    Brooks, Van Wyck Correspondence #3 (1937-1945)
    Van Wyck Brooks
  - Corres. Brown, C.B. (Box 10)
    Brown, Henry Collins
  - Corres. Miller, Marg., 1936 (Box 10)
    Miller (Mary Maur.) Little Folks in Feathers and Fun Correspondence
  - Corres. Miller, Max (Box 10)
    Miller, Max 1931-1933
    Miller, Max Fan Mail #1
    Miller, Max Fan Mail #2
    Miller, Max Fan Mail #3
  - E.P. Dutton Award, 1941; no lists, 1 letter only (Box 10)
  - Everyman's Library Memo (Box 10)
  - Finance: Debt (Box 10)
  - Finance Ide and Dutton, Inc. (Box 10)
  - French War Mission (Box 10)
  - Fragment, 1947 (Box 10)
  - Galley Proofs: Curtis Brown Publishing Bureau (Box 10)
  - "Harlem", 1940 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - "Our Mountain Garden" (Box 10)
  - Publication Schedules (Box 10)
  - Publicity - News sheets - Dutton books, 1927 (Oversize 12)
  - Publicity Releases, 1951-1959 (Box 10)
  - Royal Arcanum (Box 10)
  - Stationary - Unused, 4 folders (Box 10)
  - Terhune (Box 10)
- Authors
  - Balchen, Bernt "Come North With Me, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Beebe, Luius and Charles M. Clegg "Mixed Train Daily" photographs and artwork (Box 11)
    See also Scrapbooks: Mixed Train Daily (2 scrapbooks, Box 12).
  - Brooks, Phillips, booklet of poems (Box 11)
  - Milne, A.A., 8 folders (Box 11)
    Publication listings: The Day's Play by A.A. Milne (Box 9)
  - Sagan, 4 folders (Box 11)
    Production files: book reviews (review of Those Without Shadows, Box 28), and
    News clippings: Sagan, Françoise (Oversize 2).
  - Sagan, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Stein, Mark "The Picture Book of Wisdom", corres., receipts; bound copy of "The Picture Book of Wisdom" (Box 12)
- Scrapbooks
  - MIXED TRAIN DAILY Book I (Box 12)
  - MIXED TRAIN DAILY Book II (Box 12)
  - Under Cover, 1943-1945 (Box 12)
  - Scrapbook (Box 12)
  - Scrapbook (Box 13)
- Legal files
  - Authors: Coyle I (Box 13)
  - Authors: Coyle II (Box 13)
  - Authors: Low, Mary C. (Box 13)
  - Authorship: Danvin, "The Near East From Within" (Box 13)
  - Contracts I (Box 13)
  - Contracts II (Box 13)
  - Contracts III (Box 13)
  - Bates, Ralph (Root Clark) (Box 13)
  - Copyright violations, Hollywood Saga Digest Controversy (Box 13)
  - Indebtedness (Box 13)
  - Larceny Against E.P. Dutton, Inc. (Box 13)
  - Mr. Macrae Special, Nov. 10, 1928 (Box 13)
  - Name Change - Duttons, 1928 (Box 13)
  - Paper Appeal, 1945 (Box 13)
    Paper Request
    Information re: request for additional paper
  - Royalties - Rambo (Box 13)
  - Warrant of Attachment (Box 13)
- Stocks
  - Minute Book of E.P. Dutton and Co. (Box 14)
  - Second Minute Book Begun August 5, 1914 (Box 14)
  - Dutton Stockholder Meeting Minutes, 1928 (Box 14)
  - Minutes from Annual Meeting of Stockholders (Box 14)
    Annual Meeting of Board of Directors
    Regular Meeting of Board of Directors
  - Memorandum - from John Macrae, Sr., 1928-1943 (Box 14)
  - Memorandum - from John Macrae, Sr., 1944-1952 (Box 14)
  - Memorandum - from John Macrae, Sr., 1952-1957 (Box 14)
  - Memorandum - from John Macrae, Sr., 1957-1965 (Box 14)
  - Scrapbook - from Johnson, Blagden and Co., Inc. (Box 14)
  - Corporation Transfer Tax Record and Stock Book Combined (Box 14)
  - Book of Account, Stockbook and Stock Ledger (Box 14)
  - E.P. Dutton and Co. Stock Book (Box 14)
  - Dutton Stock Ownership, 1923-1928 (Box 14)
  - Dutton Stock Ownership, 1928 (Box 14)
  - Dutton Stock Accounts, 1944-1968 (Box 14)
  - Dutton Stock Account Book, 1919-1950; 1 volume (Oversize 17)
- Financial
  - Accounts and Book keeping, corres. legal docs., financial statements (Box 15)
  - Annual Report, 1929 (Box 15)
  - Annual Report, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Annual Report, 1932-1927 (Box 15)
  - Annual Report, 1939-1943 (Box 15)
  - Budget 1926-1927, corres. financial statements, budget report 1927 (Box 15)
  - Cash Book: Westminster Bank, 1932-1937; 1 volume (Oversize 16)
  - Checks and Receipts, corres., 1917-1926 (Box 15)
  - Christmas Bonus 1917-1929, 1931 Lists of employees and amounts paid (Box 15)
  - Profit and Loss financial reports, 1927; 1928,; 1939 (Box 15)
  - Salary, 1943; Applications, corres., lists of changes (Box 15)
  - Salary, 1944; Applications, corres., lists of changes (Box 15)
  - Salary Schedules, 1936-1939 (Box 15)
  - Taxes - 1941 corres. and 1933 tax forms (Box 15)
  - Three bound bank books, 1930-1932 (Box 15)
  - Bound book of manufacturing costs, 1874-1881 (Box 15)
  - Field Sales Book, 1929-1934 (Box 15)
  - Manufacturing Book, 1901-1906 (Box 15)
    See also Manufacturing books (Oversize 9 and 10)
  - Ledger, 1939 (Box 16)
  - Ledger, April 1941-April 1954 (Box 16)
  - Advertising Records, Late 1889-1900 (Box 16)
  - Balance Sheets, 1913-1923 (Oversize 17)
  - Ledger, June 13, 1928 - April 1941 (Box 16)
  - Ledger, June 13, 1928 - April 30, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Ledger, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Ledger, 1935 (Box 16)
  - Book - Account book 5 (Box 17)
  - Book - Account book 6 (Box 17)
  - Book - Account book 7 (Box 17)
  - Payroll, 1924-1928; 2 volumes (Oversize 16)
  - Book - Pay Roll, May 1, 1928 - Feb. 28, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Book - Pay Roll, March 7, 1930 - Oct. 31, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Book - Pay Roll, Nov. 6, 1931 - Aug. 25, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Book - Pay Roll, Sept. 1, 1933 - Aug. 30, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Book - Pay Roll, Sept. 6, 1935 - Jan. 1, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Payroll, 1937-1942; 3 volumes (Oversize 15)
  - Book - Calendars, 1897 (Box 17)
  - Book - Books, 1896 (Box 17)
  - Book - Easter, 1897 (Box 17)
  - Book - Valentines, 1897 (Box 17)
  - Book - Reward Cards, 1897 (Box 17)
  - Book - Orders: Calendars, 1899 (Box 17)
  - Book - Books, 1898 (Box 17)
  - Book - John Macrae, 1899 (Box 17)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton & Comp. John Macrae Sept. 1902 for 1903 numbers (Box 17)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton and Comp. John Macrae Valentines and Easter for 1907 (Box 18)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton and Comp. John Macrae Sept. 1908for Christmas line 1909 (Box 18)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton and Comp. John Macrae In London Sept. 1912 for Fall 1913 (Box 18)
  - Book - Valentines and Easter 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915 order placed March 1911 (Box 18)
  - Book - Christmas Line for 1914 E.P. Dutton & Comp. J.M. Feb 1914 (Box 18)
  - Book - Christmas Line for 1915 (Box 18)
  - Book - E.P. Dutton & Comp. J.M. 1914 (Box 18)
- Production files
  - Abode - Aims (Box 18)
    Abode of Snow
    A Denauer
    The Adventures of Ambrose
    Adventures of Luisa in Mexico - James
    Aesop's Fables
    Ahoy, Peggy Stewart!
    Aimez Vous Brahms Sagan
    Aims of the United Nations
  - Alexander - Alps (Box 18)
    Alexander
    All Fall Down - Herliny
    All Fall Down - Ted Key
    All That Was Mortal - David Dempsey
    Alps and Elephants - Hannibal's March
  - Amedeo - Americanization (Box 18)
    Amedeo - Daphne Barely
    Amedo
    Americanization of Emily
  - America's Arts (Box 18)
    America's Arts and Skills - Editor of LIFE
  - Anchor - Art of Makeup (Box 18)
    Anchor for Her Heart - Ellen Newcomb
    The Angel in the Hayloft - Niles
    Angels of Hudson Bay - Anderson
    Anglers and Muscleheads - Gifford
    Another Here and Now Storybook
    Antartic Adventures - Fuchs
    The Art of Makeup - Strewowski
  - Art of Writing - Beauty Markers (Box 18)
    The Art of Writing - Maurois
    Atlas of Ancient and Classical Geography
    Aurobindo Series
    Austen
    Ball for Little Bear
    Bar IV Roundup of Best Western Stories
    Bears in the Family
    Bear Twins - Hogan
    The Beauty Makers - Nedda Lamont
  - Bell - Best Detective Stories (Box 18)
    Belisarius
    A Bell for Ringelblume - Rosalie K. Fry
    Bertie Makes A Break - Felsen
    Best Detective 1957
    Best Detective Stories 1958 - 13th Annual Collection
    Best Detective Stories #16 Holiday 1961
    Best Detective Stories of the Year Boucher 19th Annual Collection
  - Best Short Stories - Big Ones (Box 18)
    Best Short Stories From the Paris Review
    Best Sport Stories - 1959 Marsh and Ehre
    Best Sport Stories - 1961 Marsh and Ehre
    Best Sport Stories - 1962 Marsh and Ehre
    The Best of W.H. Hudson - O. Shepard
    Betrothed
    Beyond The Great Slave Lake - Tom Lodge
    Big Game Animals of N.A.
    The Big Ones - Inez Hogan
  - Big Steal - Book of Party Favors (Box 18)
    The Big Steal - Basinsky
    Birthday Party and Other Stories - A.A. Milne
    The Bitter Passion - Wadleigh
    Black Spice - Steward
    The Bloody Bolchara - William Campbell Gault
    Blow the Man Down - Kuehl
    The Blus Max - Jack Hunter
    Book of Three Festivals - Lillie
    Bon Vincient, Veterinarian - E.H. Evans
    The Bold Brahmins - Lader
    Book of Party Favors and Decorations - Toni Hughes
  - Book of Verse - Canary Adventure (Box 19)
    Book of Verse for Children
    BOOM! Gralapp
    Boone of the Wilderness
    Brothers of Silence Gruber
    Bruce
    Buffalo Country - Bob Duncan
    The Bullet-proof Martyr Howard
    But Is It Deductible? Wall Street Journal
    Canary Adventures
  - Candy Kane - Child of the Dark (Box 19)
    Candy Kane
    Captain of the Queen
    Candle in the Sky
    Beverly Nichols' Cats' ABC
    The Case of the Smuggled Ruby
    Cats' XYZ
    The Centurious Larteguy
    Challenge Printing Company
    Chief of the Herd
    Child of Columbia
    Child of the Dark Carolina de Jesus
  - Children of Lilith - Combat Command (Box 19)
    The Children of Lilith - Piazzini
    Chilmark Miscelany
    Chivers' Life of Poe
    Chloe Marr
    A Choice of Heaven - Scott
    Christmas Book
    Ciano's Diary
    Circus Magic - Maillard
    Clementine
    Henry Clifford Letters
    Climatology
    To Clothe the Naked and Two Other Plays
    Clothes Make Magic
    Co-Eddiquette
    The Coffee Break - Preston
    Combat Command
  - Coming Down the Seine - Countdown For Tomorrow (Box 19)
    Coming Down the Seine by Robert Giddings
    Coming Down the Wye
    Concise Encyclopedia of Russia
    Concise Etymological Dictionary
    Conqueror
    Constance Spry Cookery Book
    Cotten Web - Hunt
    Countdown for Tomorrow - Caidin
  - Crusade and the Cup - Declaration (Box 19)
    The Crusade and the Cup
    The Cry of a Bird - Yglesias
    Curtain for Schubert
    Day Is Gone
    Day of the Phoenix
    A Death at Sea - White
    Death Haunts the Dark Lane
    Decade in Europe - Barrett McGurn
    Declaration Osborne, Wilson, et.al.
  - Defeat In The West - Eighth Day of the Week (Box 19)
    Defeat In The West
    Dixie Raider
    The Doctor and His Enemy - Alan Wykes
    Dolphin Days
    Donkey Goes Visiting
    The Doom-Maker by B.X. Sanborn
    Doughnuts for Lin
    Dulcie
    Dulcie and Her Donkey
    Dusty for Speed
    Easter Chimes
    The Eighth Day of the Week - Marek Hlasko
  - Elements of Mechanics - Everyman's English Dictionary (Box 19)
    Elements of Mechanics
    The Enchanted Castle
    The End of Loving
    English-Russian Dictionary
    Esmond by Una Troy
    Esprit De Corps - Lawrence Durrell
    Essays on the Gita - Aurobindo
    Every Common Bush
    Everyman's Dictionary of Music
    Everyman's Dictionary Quot's and Proverbs
    Everyman's English Dictionary
  - Everyman's Encyclopedia - Excursion To The Sky (Box 19)
    Everyman's Encyclopedia
    Everyman's Library - The Sea and The Jungle
    Everyman's Library Cost Tickets
    Everyman's Trademark
    An Excursion to the Sky - Olujic
  - Experiment - Five (Box 19)
    An Experiment in Mindfulness - Shattock
    Exploring for Fun - Burns
    Fairy Tales
    A Farm for Juliana
    Fighting Crime
    Finger Prints - Douglas Browne and Alan Brock
    First Christmas
    First Prize For Danny
    Five on a Merry - Go - Round
  - Five Day - Gobbling (Box 19)
    The Five-Day Nightmare - Brown
    Floreana - Wittmar
    The Flower in the Gutter
    Foodarama Party Book
    Footlights for Mary
    For Each Other - Janet Lambert Spring '59
    Forever Possess
    Foundation of Tibetan Mysticism
    Fourteen Men
    Friend to All
    Galleys - Cost
    Giants of China
    Gift of Life
    Giotto Tended the Sheep
    Glory Be!
    The Gobbling Billy - James
  - Golden - Green (Box 19)
    Golden Apples of the Sun
    The Goodly Seed
    Grameray Park - Gladys Brooks
    A Grave Undertaking - White
    The Graveyard - Flasko
    Great Prisoners
    The Greek Affair - Frank Gruger Fall '64
    The Green Man From Mars - Lewis Zarem (Space)
  - Growth - He (Box 19)
    Growth of a Nation
    The Gypsies
    Hanover's Wishing Star
    The Haunted Isle
    Haunted People
    Heather Mary
    Henry James; Selected Fiction EML 649 A
    He Went For A Walk
  - Here's - Horn (Box 20)
    Here's Looking At You Fall '64 (cartoons from WSJ-Preston, ed.)
    Hermit In The Himalayas
    Hi! Barney!
    Hidalgo and The Gringo Man by Fay Griffith. Ills. Karl Oechsli
    History of the Maryknoll Sisters - Maryknoll Sisters
    History of the Royal and Ancient Game of Golf
    Hitler and His Admirals
    Hogan
    Horace
    The Horn and The Sword by Jack Randolph Conrad
  - Horns - Hundred-Dollar (Box 20)
    The Horns of Fear - de Lera
    Horse Haven
    The Horseman's Dict. Bloodgood and Santini
    Hot For Certainties Robin Douglas-Home
    House of the 1,000 Pleasures - Harris
    How to Gain An Extra Hour - Kay Josephs
    How to Help the Shut in Child
    How You Can Find Happiness
    Hudson Copyrights
    Huffley Fair - Dorthy Evelyn Smith
    The Human Cycle - Aurobindo
    Hums of Pooh
    The Hundred-Dollar Girl - Gault
  - Ideal - It (Box 20)
    Ideal of Human Unity
    If You Like Hazel
    I Give You My Word and Say the Word
    Image of Hell - Fisher
    The Improper Bohemians - Allen Churchill
    Introduction to Kierkegaard
    Isis And Cosiris by Hyde
    I, The Jury
    It Happened to Hannah
    It Is Not So Easy to Live - Arnothy
  - It's - Joseph (Box 20)
    It's All In The Family (Project - 1958)
    It's Still In The Family - Berenstains
    Jefferson Reader
    Job of Living by White
    John Sloan
    Johnswood by Charlie May Sunon
    Joseph Boliver de Lee By Fishbein
  - Journey - Kennedy (Box 20)
    Journey to Christmas - B.J. Chute
    Journey to Persia
    Joy to My Youth
    Juan of Manila by McSwigan
    Jump For Joy
    Just Jennifer by Lambert
    Kangchenjunga
    The Kennedy Government - Opotowsky
  - Kicking - Leap (Box 20)
    Kicking Canvas by Captain A.A. Bestic
    A Kid for Two Farthings - Wolf Mankowitz
    King of the Mountain
    La Belle - Coker
    The Lady and The Corsair - J.M. Scott
    Lady Rich - Coker
    Land of Nursery Rhymes
    Land of Sky Blue Waters
    The Late Lamented - Brown
    Latin America New Revised Edition - Schurz
    Latin Key to Better English
    Leap Through The Curtain
  - Learning - Little (Box 20)
    Learning About Love
    Letter to a Niece
    Life and Times of the Buckshot South - Frank Davis Adams
    Lines of Least Resistance
    The Lion's Share - Crowther
    Literary Criticisms